the three most famous candidates who
три самых известных кандидата которые
will run as
будут баллотироваться как конкуренты
Putin's competitors Hello Hello I'm from the city of
Путина Здравствуйте Привет Я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from in the
Хмельницкий Вы откуда серпу в
Moscow suburbs Moscow suburbs yes And what city
Подмосковье Подмосковье да А какой город
And Serpukhov Serpukhov I know is a very
А Серпухов Серпухов знаю очень
historical city Yes there are no such
исторический город Да там нету таких
problems as in Podolsk in
проблем как в Подольске в
Khimki there are problems
Химках проблемы есть
everywhere Well, like this  that
везде Ну а типа такое что без отопления
they were left without heating
остались
in the meniscus No problem Well, we don’t have any, we do
в мениском Нет проблем Ну у нас не
n’t know, we
остаются у нас не знаю у нас
even had bombings, but no one
бомбардировки даже были но никакие никто
sat without heat, but in Russia I
без тепла не сидел а вот в России что-то
see something in Serpukhov, I say there is a
смотрю у вас в Серпухове говорю есть
heating shutdown like in Podolsk Well,
отключение отопления как в Подольске Ну
no  I know Open the sites there, not with us, everything is
не знаю Открой сайты там не у нас всё
fine, everything is fine, and what do you communicate with? Well,
прекрасно всё прекрасно а чём общаетесь
it all depends on the interlocutors. Well,
Ну а всё зависит от собеседников Ну вот
with me, with me. What do you want to
а со мной со мной Чем хотите
communicate with? Yes, I don’t know how it is with you. Come
пообщаться Да я не знаю как у тебя Ну
on. That’s what you came here for. Come on, let’s be
давайте Вот для чего вы вышли сюда давай
politicians. Let’s be politicians.  let's give
политики Давай политики давайте давайте
me the name of Putin's main competitors
можете мне назвать основных конкурентов
in
Путина на
the elections Do you want to talk about our politics Well, yes,
выборах А ты хочешь о наше полити Ну да
politicians, yes, you have elections We wo
политики да у вас же выборы Скоро у нас
n't have elections soon, I know I'm strong with this As they
не скоро я знаешь я сильно этим Как
say, it's not
говорится не
dawn I heard because of Nadezhdin's position,
зарю Я слышал изза позиции надеждин там
who was
выдвинулся кто такой
Nadezhdin Nadezhdin?  he was flashing here on
надеждин надеждин Да он тут по
TV Well, who is he, at
телевизору мелькал Ну такой кто он его
least someone knows who Nadezhdin is Yes, I
хоть кто-то знает кто такой надеждин Да
don’t know Well, who is he? Well, some kind of
не знаю Ну кто он Ну какой-то
oppositionist, what party does he
оппозиционер какую он партию
represent? I could be wrong, but
представляет Я могу ошибиться но
in my opinion, I understand the nomination itself.
по-моему само выдвижение по-моему понял
Although maybe that is  in short, Putin’s
Хотя может то есть короче у Путина
main competitor is whose main competitor even you don’t
основной конкурент которого даже вы не
really know.
знаете толком
No, he has a competitor there, I
Да нет там конкурент у него есть там я
know them,
их знаю
but there, firstly, every party except the
но там во-первых каждая партия кроме
fair one nominated its leaders. Name Name
справедливый выдвинул своих лидеров вот
who was nominated there from the
Назовите Назовите кого выдвинули там из
well-known ones Well, come on Kharitonov, in my opinion, the
известных так Ну давай Харитонов
Communist Party of the Russian Federation  And who is Kharitonov,
по-моему КПРФ А кто такой Харитонов у
they have Zyuganov
них же Зюганов
Leader Zyuganov decided
Лидер Зюганов решил
to move neighed
двигать
like that Zyuganov decided to move [ __ ] dude
заржал такой Зюганов решил двигать Бля
You’re just a hundred move
чувак Ты просто сто двигать
young people Kharitonov himself is not that
молодёжь Харитонов сам не такой уж
young, poet
молодёжь поэто
dadada
дадада
Khariton That’s the dude You drove
харитона Вот это чувак Ты погнал
Krug exactly not well, just as it is I
Круга именно не ну то да как есть я же
laughed myself  what is there Not I'm serious
сам засмеялся то что есть Не я серьёзно
You're real Why count it as so good uh
Ты реально Зачем зачесть на так хорошо э
Perov And others What parties Who else
Перов А другие Какие партии Кто ещё кого
nominated whom from the famous LDPR LDPR Who
выдвинул из известных ЛДПР ЛДПР Кого
nominated Lutsky Who Lutsky who is this guy
выдвинула луцкого Кого луцкий кто это
anyway
вообще
Leader instead of Zhirinovsky that is, a
такой ну Лидер вместо Жириновского то то
dude whom no one really
есть чувак которого вообще никто толком
knows
не знает
Well, someone
ну кто-то
knows, in short, it’s like
знает короче онно типа
yes Well, maybe who else are you? I don’t know,
да Ну может ещё кто вы Я не знаю просто
I just look, I don’t remember When we
я смотрю не я вспоминаю Когда у нас
had elections, but we have a damn bunch of
выборы были да вот у нас блин куча
candidates, each candidate has
кандидатов каждый кандидат имеет
some chance, well-known personalities there,
какие-то шансы известные личности там
Poroshenko Zelensky, Pritula there,
Порошенко Зеленский Притула там
Tymoshenko  in America Yes, the candidates are well-
Тимошенко в Америке Да кандидаты
known there, some there to
известные там какие-то там
whom, I’m telling you Tymoshenko Yes,
к кто е я же говорю Тимошенко Да
all the well-known personalities are
притулок все известные личности
all known, yes And you have
все извест г да А у вас
some stupid, some no-names, your what did you
какие-то тупо какие-то
call her, the woman with the
ноунеймы ваша как ты её назвал женщина с
oblique, how old is she putting forward how many
косой лет она выдвигает сколько сколько
150 years old, that is, Wait, you are now
лет 150 то есть Подождите вы сейчас
Putin Putin is older than Tymoshenko Yes And
Путин Путин старше Тимошенко Да И
your woman says askance she is 150 years old
говорите ваша женщина с косо ей 150 лет
and you are
а вы она
moving forward look Well, we have
выдвигается смотри Ну вот какой-то у нас
some kind of uninteresting conversation there is a
это такой ну неинтересный разговор есть
much more interesting interesting one no no
намного интереснее интересный нене не
wait this is an interesting election look
подожди это интересный выборы смотри
Elections  - this is now the very most important
Выборы - это сейчас очень самая главная
political agenda of the Russian
политическая повестка Российской
Federation, this is the elections, yes, that is, will they
Федерации это ж выборы да то есть
elect Putin, yes Or maybe there on I
изберут ли Путина да А может там на Я
saw there is also a gladness of the Russians there, yes
видел там ещё это рада русских есть да
such a candidate was seen,
такая кандидатка видели
the blogger was not seen, yes I understood about I thought I
блогерша не видели да понял о Я думал Я
thought maybe in short there Is  there are also such
думал может короче там Есть ещё такие
candidates there Udaltsov Nemtsov uh this
кандидаты там Удальцов Немцов э этот
Navalny they are not running they
Навальный они не баллотируются они
know the dead only maybe Biden has
знаете покойники только могут быть у
understood yes No well this uh Nemtsov was
байдена понял да Не ну этот э Немцова то
killed yes And for example Navalny is alive Yes
убили да А например Навальный живой Да
Udaltsov alive was also
Удальцов живой тоже
arrested And for example I I heard that
арестовали А например я Я слышал что
Strelkov wanted to run for President  and
стрелков хотел идти в Президент и
collected signatures and refused
собирали подписи и отказали в
registration he
регистрации ему
heard
слышали
this heard And why are these the heroes of
такое слышал А почему это вот герои
Novorossiya Igor
новороссии Игорю
Strelkovaya presidential candidates
стрелковую кандидаты в президенты
Why I don’t have complete information That’s why
Почему я не обладаю полной информации
I’m here like th Well, that
Поэтому я тут как
means he screwed up something Wait,
ть Ну значит он что-то накосячил Подожди
why is he even a hero of Novorossiya
а почему его вообще героя новоросси
who fought for
который боролся за
russian sio why Well, well, I’m saying something,
руский сио почему Ну ну я говорю что-то
someone screwed up Well, that’s not right, why is
кто-то накосячил к Ну не так за что
this Strelkov being held in a pre-trial detention center who was
этого Стрелкова держат в СИЗО кого у вас
killed yesterday? Wait Stop stop stop don’t run away do
вчера убили Подожди Стоп стоп стоп не
n’t run away you see I just
убегай не убегай видишь я тебя просто
fried you and now you want to run away from
прожарил и ты сейчас хочешь убежать от
the discussion  Russian politics Yes,
обсуждение российской политики Да
run away you you kun you will run away if you don’t kun
убежать ты ты кун ты убежишь если не кун
Let’s settle this why Strelkov,
Давай договорим это почему Стрелкова
who wants to be a
который хочет быть кандидатом в
presidential candidate, is kept in prison in a pre-trial detention
президенты держат в тюрьме в
center
СИЗО
I don’t know exactly how many million we have in prison,
Я не знаю сколько точно у нас в тюрьме
maybe half a million,
находится миллион может полмиллиона
maybe all half a million want to be
может быть все полмиллиона хотят быть
president but they  for some reason they are sitting in
президентом но они почему-то сидят в
prison, yes, why with I just see
тюрьме вот да почему с Я просто смотрю
that
что все
everyone means they violated the Criminal
какие-то значит они нарушили Уголовный
Code and therefore are sitting in prison Dada, what did
кодекс и поэтому сидят в тюрьме Дада что
the shooters violate, what am
нарушил стрелков
I, a prosecutor or lawyer, shooter Well, this is the
что я что прокурор или адвокат стрелко
hero of Naro, he’s still behind Go to the Internet
Ну это герой Наро он ещё зади В интернет
If  you're wondering
зайди Если тебе интересно что нарушил
what law a specific character broke What law I'm
Какой закон конкретный персонаж Я же
not a lawyer for you no So yes I watched I
тебе не юрист нет Так я да я смотрел я
watched I'm a lawyer I watched in this thread
смотрел Я юрист Я в этой теме смотрел за
because he wrote something in a telegram Well, [ __ ]
то что он в телеграме писал что-то Ну ну
him I'm not interested you know A
хуй на него мне не интересно понимаешь А
good A  look And I also heard that, uh, I
хорошо А смотрите А я ещё слышал что ээ
wanted to run for president, such
хотел баллотируется в президент такой
Evgeniy Prigozhin, maybe you remember there was such a
Евгений Пригожин может помните был такой
PMC Wagner, you don’t know why he was killed.
чвк Вагнер не знаете почему его убили
You heard the official version. Which one have
Ты слышал официальную версию
n’t you heard? No, the EU is
Какая не слышал Нет вот ЕС тебе
interesting for you. Go to the
интересно Зайди в
Internet, I know there was an explosion on the plane where
интернет знаю был взрыв в самолёте где
they were flying. What?  exploded on the plane
они летели А что взорвалось в самолёте
by accident again there was one message and
случайно опять там было одно сообщение а
then there was a message it was over it wasn’t over I
потом было сст кончилось не закончилось
also don’t know when the investigation
Я тоже не знаю когда следствие
will end there it’s definitely all lying down Po A I understood I understood that is,
закончится там точно всё ложит По По А
everything is there, that is,
понял понял понял то есть там всё раз то
look I see that everyone is
есть смотрите Я так смотрю что все
some kind of famous  personalities there
какие-то известные личности там
Navalny put the
Навальный посадили
shooters behind Novoro since
стрелков за Новоро ещё с четырнадцатого
1914 Donbass defended they put a
года Донбасс защищал посадили
spoon Prigozhin killed
ложка Пригожин убили
Loka only Putin and some
лока остался только Путин и какието
no-names left are somehow interesting well damn it’s just that
ноунеймы как-то интересно ну блин просто
some of your elections are boring Yes, that’s all I am It
аж какие-то выборы скучные у вас Да все
seems to me that
вот я Мне кажется что мне скучны
talking with me is boring  you to me S And what
разговор с тобой мне С А что скучно
immediately became boring Why did it become boring and why did you
сразу стало Почему стало скучно а что ты
choose one topic and dadada so let’s
тему выбрал и одну а дадада так вот
talk yes well, really look
давай поговорим да ну реально смотри у
you just have elections on the horizon elections
вас у вас просто выборы на носу выборы
so I’ll tell you about the elections and I
вот я тебе про выборы скажу и больше я к
won’t go back to them anymore  I’ll be like
ним Возвращаться не буду так давай
this, let’s look, let’s talk about the elections, we realized that
смотри давай про выборы мы поняли что ня
no No, look again, no, no, wait,
не Нет ещё раз смотри не не чува подожди
you won’t run away, you won’t run away I’m talking about elections, I’m
ты ты не убежишь ты не убежишь Я про
talking about elections, I’m talking about elections, there were
выборы говорю выборы Я про выборы были
elections before this, 4 years ago there were
были выборы до этого 4 года назад были
elections, a friend came to me then
выборы ко мне пришёл друг тогда ещё
Grudinin was also nominated, a lot of
выдвигался грудинин такой за него много
people voted for him, and so we sat and he was like,
кто голосовал и вот мы сидели и он типа
you should be for Grudinin, they
как ты вот за грудинин должен за него
should be more for him, something’s wrong, it was
должны больше что-то не так это ещё было
before the elections there, well, a week or so, back and
до выборов там ну за неделю где-то
forth. By the way,
туда-сюда
mine, too, that time for the
Я кстати по-моему тоже в тот раз за
sternum Well, in my opinion, yes, I also voted for the sternum for
грудини Ну по-моему да за грудини тоже
a year, look Let’s
голосовал я год вот смотри Давай вот так
figure it out like this, let’s figure it out, let’s
вот разберёмся давай разберёмся вот
take all my As they say, my relatives are two
возьмём всю мою Как говорится родню двое
children, my wife is my father’s mother-in-law Well, I have a lot of
детей жена тёщу отца Ну много у меня
relatives I’m telling you, I’ll tell you
родственников Я говорю я тебе буду
who is for whom exactly exactly for the
говорить кто за кого точно тщ точно за
way
пути
8 you have [ __ ] here the people of the Armed Forces are equally for
8 у тебя тут [__] люди ВС равно за
Putin then and now you understand
Путина тогда и сейчас понимаешь
80% of the population will be for Putin now
80% населения оно будет за Путина сейчас
this is grinding no one
вот это перемалывать никого
neres voted last time for
нерес голосовали прошлый раз за
breasts
груди
about breasts I can even tell you
про груди я тебе могу даже сказать
Tell you you  Maybe you know,
Расскажите ты ты может быть знаешь есть
we have a businessman like that, and you,
у нас бизнесмен такой который и у вас
too, have a [ __ ] glow on your bloggers.
тоже у блогеров
Yesterday I was just listening to your
светится бля Вчера только слушал у ва
last name being Ukrainian. Well, okay, that’s
уше фамилия украинскую Ну ладно вот ито
the question, how different was the question from the
вопрос как разн был уше ему вопрос из
chat, they said to him, But Breastin there, what are you doing
чата говорили А вот грудин там что ты
back and forth with him?  this is a little hurt, he
там туда-сюда его это маленько задел он
says, and the First Rudy is my
говорит а Первый Руди Это мой
relative [ __ ] VS, I remember the last
родственник бляд ВС фамилию вспоминаю
name, but you’re sitting here,
известно вот а вы вот сидите тут пиздите
you’re [ __ ] up, you don’t even help a penny to
вы даже копейки не помо чтобы
run for
баллотироваться на
president you need a minimum oh how much did he
президента нужно минимум ой сколько он
say 3 million or something, it’s not so
сказал 3 млн что ли там не так всё
simple 300,000 votes signatures  there he
просто 300000 голосов подписи там он
says: “You help,
говорит Вот вы помогите
not with words, [ __ ], but donate a penny,
не словами [__] А копеечки внесите мы
then we’ll
тогда
put forward in order to take part in the
выдвиньте чтобы чтобы принять участие в
voting, firstly, you need the number of
голосовании во-первых нужно количество
votes to collect real ones, not fake ones,
голосов собрать настоящих не поддельных
and you need to have a certain level of money
и нужно иметь определённый уровень денег
to start this election race.
чтобы начать вот эту предвыборную гонку
Not everyone can do it, but here many  let
Не каждый это сможет а тут многие вот
’s say, probably Udaltsov. I don’t know
допустим наверное Удальцов Я не знаю
if he has this money, first of all,
если у него во-первых вот эти деньги
so many signatures, he
столько он подпис он
can close the CA, well, no, that’s not the point, maybe
может закрыли УЦ всё ну Нет дело не в
they didn’t even close it. But does he have it? He can collect so many
ли у него это сможет Он набрать столько
signatures; the source has capital  This is
подписей исток имеет капитал Это большой
Navalny’s big question Yes, he was
вопрос Навального Да его там
sponsored by the West, he probably
спонсировали Запад у него наверное всё
could have had everything there And they’re talking about Sivka
там могло бы быть А эти они так Сивки вя
and that’s it Well, okay, let’s do it There is
кают и всё Ну ладно всё давай Есть тема
another topic, let’s not let us, we’re still
другая есть давай не давай мы всё-таки
pushing Russian politics, you’re just a
до жмём российскую политику просто вы
very interesting person  because you
очень интересный человек потому что вы
understand Russian politics
разбираетесь в Российской политике Да
Yes, Putin must live to win, there’s nothing to clamp down on here Let’s then let’s
зажимать с вот Давайте тогда э сделаем
finalize
так финализировать
three candidates against Putin Name those
против Путина три кандидата Назовите
who are strong and run against
которые сильны идут против
Putin And what does it mean against Putin, everyone
Путина А что значит против Путина каждый
goes their own way yes yes who who is
идёт своей по да да кто кто
also running for  elections Yes, as it were,
баллотируется тоже на выборы Да как бы
Putin’s competitor Yes, here are the top three
конкурент Путина Да вот топ три самых
three strongest
Три сильных
candidates Look, firstly, there is
кандидатов Вот смотри во-первых есть
an opposition and there are non-systemic oppositions That’s
оппозиция а есть несистемные оппозиции
what you say Navalny Udaltsova
Вот как ты говоришь Навальный Удальцова
And so on, this is not a systemic opposition
И тому прочее это не системная оппозиция
But there is an opposition These are the parties that
А есть оппозиция Вот как раз эти партии
nominate their own As they say
выдвигают своих Как говорится
representatives they are opposition
представителей они оппозиции
three, name three names three names of
три назовите три фамилии три фамилии
the most Three strong candidates who
самых Три сильных кандидата которые
will compete with Putin in the elections
конкуренты Путину на выборах будут
look if Putin gets 80% of
ри смотри если Путин набирает 80%
the votes remaining How many votes are 20% Yes,
голосов остаётся Сколько голосов 20% Да
and if 20% are scattered among everyone, then which ones are
и если 20% раскидать на всех то какие
strong for the groom, let’s do so Who is the most
сильны давайте так к Кто самый
izva  was strong Let's name the three
изва был сильны Давайте Т назовите три
most famous Let's not say the three
самых известных Давайте пусть не си три
most famous candidates who will
самых известных кандидата которые будут
run as
баллотироваться как конкуренты
Putin's competitors I
Путина я те
said
сказал
everything nadezhdinski Kharitonov trino name
всё надеждин ски Харитонов трино нейма
understood I got it and something went out Yes from these
понял Понял да что-то потухли Да от этих
conversations it’s already a little Well it’s
разговоров уже немножко Да ну оно
not interesting You’re here  Here is
неинтересно Ты вот Вот
muso because, well, I want to
мусо потому что ну я хочу
watch X we don’t discuss this topic, I do
смотреть Х эту тему не обсуждаем она Я
n’t want to discuss it superficially Yes, discuss the topic
хочу не поверхностно Да обговорить тему
But go deeper and expand and
А углубиться да расширить и
deepen, you know Well,
углубить
first of all, look, first of all, everyone
понимаете Ну во-первых смотри вопервых
has united around Putin’s strategy,
вокруг стратегии Путина все объединились
and if suddenly a new strong,
так и если вдруг рождается новый сильный
charismatic leader is born, He must  provide some kind of
харизматичный лидер Он должен какую-то
agenda to the people so that
повестку народу предоставить такую чтобы
it differs from Putin’s Well, so
она и отличалась от путино ской Ну и
that the people accept it firstly and there is
чтобы народ её принял во-первых и
no such person and there is no such program
личности такой нет и программы такой
here Navalny has the same person
тут Навальный личность такая его же
on purpose and that’s why he’s keeping him in prison
специально поэтому и держит в тюрме
so that he can’t Well, understand, wait  Well, let’s say
чтобы он не могти Ну пойми подожди Ну
if For me, he Look For
допустим вот если Для меня он Смотри Для
me, let’s say he was released, he’s
меня допустим его выпустили он сейчас
on his way now Yes, what can he offer me? So you have
идёт Да что мне может предложить Так вам
nothing, but a lot of people, a lot of people can
ничего но куча людей куча людей может
offer Well, of course, the youth will
предложить Ну может конечно молодёжь он
say Let’s stop the war again Ay, date,
скажет Давайте опять войну прекратим Ай
put up with the [ __ ] West We
дате мириться с западом [__] Опять
’ll be an appendage again  and which part
будем придатком и какая часть за ним
will follow him There is no market Yeah Well, I understand And
пойдёт Базара нет Угу Ну понял А
look, I understand correctly that
смотрите вот я правильно понимаю что
Putin is not eternal, so for example,
Путин же не вечный так вот например а
imagine if Putin dies before the elections,
представьте если Путин да до выборов
if oh, if Putin before the elections I’m not
умрёт если пу если Путин до выборов Я
eternal either Yes, but I’m not
тоже не вечный Да но я не
running, look  look
баллотируется вот смотрите смотрите
now Nadezhdin has come forward there
сейчас выдвинулся там вот надеждин
look Nadezhdin Kharitonov Slutsky Yes,
смотрите надеждин Харитонов Слуцкий Да
for which of these three Nadezhdin
за кого бы из этих трёх Вот надеждин
Kharitonov Slutsky would you
Харитонов слуцки за ко бы вы
vote for
проголосовали
Eva Ukraine Look, come on, I understand Well, I
Еву Украину Смотри вот давай я понял Ну
don’t have
не
hopes, I’m not a
надежды я не
Dreamer, let’s do this if I play along, I
Фантазёр давайте так если подыгрывать я
won’t And why are you afraid  lie down Why are
не бу А почему ты боишься ложись Почему
you really afraid? Let's do this if Putin
ты боишься реально Давай так если Путин
withdraws his candidacy from the elections, he
снимает свою кандидатуру с выборов
says, I'm tired, I'm in good health. Sun
говорит я устал у меня здоровье там ВС
Yes For whom?
Да За кого Про
We won't let him vote for
голосуете мы ему не
no Putin I don't allow you Yes, you
нет Путин Я тебе не разрешаю
'll do a rally Yes, let
Да митинг митинг сделаете
's go home, open up the apartment
Да идём домой вскроем квартиру
Come on Oh slaves slaves
Давай Ой рабы рабы
slaves just a slave slave
рабы просто раб раб
timid oh al cool we fried the dude
робей ой ал классно мы чувака прожарили
Yes, he goes to chat roulette to
Да он выходит в чат рулетку чтобы про
talk about Ukraine what’s there about us what’s there
Украину поговорить что там о нас что там
And here oh How unpleasant Yes, when they
А тут ой Как неприятно Да когда тебя
pick at you about Russian politics, it seems like there are
ковыряют по российской политике кажется
no elections and some candidates Well  I already
и выборов нет да и кандидаты какие-то Ну
laughed myself Yes, when
аж сам засмеялся Да когда
Ghana’s high, high, high, put a plus to whomever
ганов кайф кайф кайф поставьте плюс кому
you’ve enjoyed This dialogue, put a plus sign and
сподобався Цей диалог поставьте плюсик и
delete the comment Yes, subscribe to th
залиште комент Да подпишись на й
Telegram right away, he’s even
Telegram прям зараз он а
more and more
пок це дуже и дуже
polite
важливо